Now let's take a deep dive into the program,
下面我们介绍下这门课程
and talk about what you will learn in the next few months.
并讨论下你将在接下来的几个月学习的内容
First of all, to get the most out of this program,
首先 要从这门课程中学到更多知识
you'll ideally have Intermediate Python skills including Numpy and Pandas,
你需要掌握中级 Python 技能 包括 NumPy 和 Pandas
and prior exposure to statistics,
并且熟悉统计学
linear algebra, and calculus.
线性代数和微积分
We've designed this program to be accessible to anyone who is passionate
这门课程面向渴望利用
about using advanced data analytics to make sense of financial data.
高级数据分析技巧研究金融数据的任何人
With that in mind, we will review certain bath encoding concepts as they are
所以 我们将复习某些编程概念
used or point you to other Udacity resources to refresh your background knowledge.
并提供其他优达学城资料链接 供你复习这些知识
The Nadir degree program has two terms.
这门纳米学位课程分为 2 个学期
Each term contains four projects and will take three months to complete.
每学期都包含 4 个实战项目 将持续 3 个月
Prior to each project,
在实战项目之前
there's a set of lessons, quizzes,
我们会提供一系列课程 小测验和练习
and exercises that will introduce you to a topic and prepare you for the project.
从而向你介绍某个主题知识并使你为项目做好准备
You will then practice what you've learned by completing the project.
然后你将运用所学的知识完成项目
Note that much of your learning will come from working on the project,
注意 为了巩固所学的知识
trying different things and even going
你需要完成项目 尝试不同的方法
beyond what is required as you explore what's possible.
甚至超出课程的要求范畴
We highly encourage you to take the time,
我们强烈建议你
to make each project your own unique
将精力花在认真完成项目上
reflection of what you have learned and what you are capable of.
并通过项目展示你的独特技能
Students who successfully complete term one are eligible to enroll in term two.
成功学完第一学期的学员将有资格报名第二学期
At the end of term two,
在第二学期结束时
you will embark on a Capstone Project which will give you the opportunity to use
你将完成一个毕业项目
everything you've learned to design and evaluate quantitative trading strategies.
届时你将有机会运用所学的所有知识设计和评估量化交易策略
In term one, you will learn about the Fundamentals of Quantitative Finance.
在第一学期 你将学习量化投资的基础知识
You will apply quantitative methods that are practiced in
你将运用金融行业用到的量化投资方法
the financial industry including regression,
包括回归、优化
optimization, and trading signal generation.
以及交易信号生成
You will work on projects that reflect
在实战项目中
the actual quant workflow as it's done in financial firms,
你将对真实数据集应用在金融公司中
with real data sets.
采用的实际量化分析工作流程
Term one is designed to prepare you for term two,
第一学期将为第二学期打下基础
which applies more advanced methods to the quant workflow.
第二学期会对量化分析工作流程应用更高级的方法
In term two, you'll use machine learning algorithms to generate trading signals.
在第二学期 你将使用机器学习算法生成交易信号
You'll use natural language processing to analyze
你将利用自然语言处理技巧
financial statements and apply recurrent neural networks to analyze news data.
分析财务报表并利用递归神经网络分析新闻数据
You'll get hands on practice with backtesting,
你将进行回溯测试实践练习
which is a realistic simulation designed to evaluate the effectiveness of a strategy.
回溯测试是一种现实模拟 旨在评估某个策略的效果
Finally, you will use advanced techniques to
最后 你将运用进阶技巧
combine several trading signals together to optimize a portfolio.
将多个交易信号组合到一起并优化投资组合
We hope that sounds exciting to you.
希望你能对这些知识感兴趣
We can't wait to see you in the classroom.
迫不及待地想要在课堂中见到你了